<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Introduction on WebLogic Kubernetes Operator</title>
    <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/userguide/introduction/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Introduction on WebLogic Kubernetes Operator</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/userguide/introduction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Important terms</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/userguide/introduction/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 16:43:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/userguide/introduction/terms/</guid>
      <description>This documentation uses several important terms which are intended to have a specific meaning.
   Term Definition     Cluster Because this term is ambiguous, it will be prefixed to indicate which type of cluster is meant. A WebLogic cluster is a group of WebLogic Managed Servers that together host some application or component and which are able to share load and state between them; a single WebLogic domain can define multiple WebLogic clusters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design philosophy</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/userguide/introduction/design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 20:51:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/userguide/introduction/design/</guid>
      <description>The WebLogic Kubernetes Operator (the “operator”) is designed to fulfill a similar role to that which a human operator would fill in a traditional data center deployment. It contains a set of useful built-in knowledge about how to perform various life cycle operations on a domain correctly.
Human operators are typically responsible for starting and stopping environments, performing scaling operations, performing manual tasks associated with disaster recovery and high availability needs and coordinating actions with other operators in other data centers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Architecture</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/userguide/introduction/architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 20:51:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/userguide/introduction/architecture/</guid>
      <description>Contents  Overall architecture Domain architecture Domain UID Network name predictability Domain state stored outside container images  Overall architecture The operator consists of the following parts:
 The operator runtime, which is a process that:  Runs in a container deployed into a Kubernetes Pod and that monitors one or more Kubernetes namespaces. Performs the actual management tasks for domain resources deployed to these namespaces.   A Helm chart for installing the operator runtime and its related resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get help</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/userguide/introduction/get-help/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 16:43:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/userguide/introduction/get-help/</guid>
      <description>Oracle Slack We have a closely monitored public Slack channel where you can get in touch with us to ask questions about using the operator or give us feedback or suggestions about what features and improvements you would like to see. We can also create dedicated private channels upon request. We would love to hear from you.
To join our public channel, please visit this site to get an invitation. The invitation email will include details of how to access our Slack workspace.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
