<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WebLogic Kubernetes Operator</title>
    <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/index.html</link>
    <description>The WebLogic Kubernetes Operator (the “operator”) supports running your WebLogic Server and Fusion Middleware Infrastructure domains on Kubernetes, an industry standard, cloud neutral deployment platform. It lets you encapsulate your entire WebLogic Server installation and layered applications into a portable set of cloud neutral images and simple resource description files. You can run them on any on-premises or public cloud that supports Kubernetes where you’ve deployed the operator.&#xA;Furthermore, the operator is well suited to CI/CD processes. You can easily inject changes when moving between environments, such as from test to production. For example, you can externally inject database URLs and credentials during deployment, or you can inject arbitrary changes to most WebLogic configurations.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 17:34:48 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Quick Start</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/quickstart/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/quickstart/index.html</guid>
      <description>The Quick Start guide provides a simple tutorial to help you get the operator up and running quickly. Use this Quick Start guide to create a WebLogic Server deployment in a Kubernetes cluster with the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator (the “operator”). Please note that this walk-through is for demonstration purposes only, not for use in production. These instructions assume that you are already familiar with Kubernetes. If you need more detailed instructions, please refer to Manage operators .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/introduction/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/introduction/index.html</guid>
      <description>Gain an overall understanding of the operator and learn where you can get help.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage operators</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/managing-operators/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 16:43:38 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/managing-operators/index.html</guid>
      <description>Install, configure, and manage the operator.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage domains</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/managing-domains/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 16:43:45 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/managing-domains/index.html</guid>
      <description>Managing domains in Kubernetes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WebLogic images</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/base-images/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 16:45:55 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/base-images/index.html</guid>
      <description>Obtain, create, and dynamically patch images for WebLogic Server or Fusion Middleware Infrastructure deployments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samples</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/samples/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:28:03 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/samples/index.html</guid>
      <description>The samples provide demonstrations of how to accomplish common tasks. These samples are provided for educational and demonstration purposes only; they are not intended to be used in production deployments or to be depended upon to create production environments.&#xA;CredentialsSample for creating a Kubernetes Secret that contains the Administration Server credentials. This Secret can be used in creating a WebLogic Domain YAML file.&#xA;StorageSample for creating a PV or PVC that can be used by a Domain YAML file as the persistent storage for the WebLogic domain home or log files.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer Guide</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/developerguide/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:54 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/developerguide/index.html</guid>
      <description>The Developer Guide provides information for developers who want to understand or contribute to the code.&#xA;Contribute to the operatorLearn how to contribute to the operator project.&#xA;RequirementsReview the software requirements to obtain and build the operator.&#xA;BuildingLearn about the operator build process.&#xA;Integration testsLearn about the available Java integration tests.&#xA;BranchingUnderstand the operator repository branching strategy.&#xA;Coding standardsReview the project coding standards.&#xA;Code structureReview the project directory structure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reference</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/reference/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 16:16:39 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/reference/index.html</guid>
      <description>See the following reference documentation.&#xA;Domain resourceUse this document to set up and configure your own YAML file containing Domains and Clusters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/security/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 17:34:48 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/security/index.html</guid>
      <description>CertificatesOperator SSL/TLS certificate handling.&#xA;Domain securityWebLogic domain security and the operator.&#xA;EncryptionWebLogic domain encryption and the operator.&#xA;Service accountsKubernetes ServiceAccounts for the operator.&#xA;RBACOperator role-based authorization.&#xA;SecretsKubernetes Secrets for the operator.&#xA;OpenShiftOpenShift information for the operator.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequently asked questions</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/faq/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 08:14:59 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/faq/index.html</guid>
      <description>This section provides answers to frequently asked questions.&#xA;Answers for newcomersAnswers to commonly asked newcomer questions.&#xA;Cannot pull imageMy domain will not start and I see errors like `ImagePullBackoff` or `Cannot pull image`.&#xA;Boot identity not validOne or more WebLogic Server instances in my domain will not start and I see errors in the server log like this: `Boot identity not valid`.&#xA;Domain secret mismatchOne or more WebLogic Server instances in my domain will not start and the domain resource `status` or the pod log reports errors like this: Domain secret mismatch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deprecated functionality</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/deprecated-functionality/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 08:14:59 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/deprecated-functionality/index.html</guid>
      <description>The following functionality has been deprecated and no longer is supported in WebLogic Kubernetes Operator.&#xA;Domain in Image The Domain in Image domain home source type is deprecated in WebLogic Kubernetes Operator version 4.0. Oracle recommends that you choose either Domain on PV or Model in Image, depending on your needs.&#xA;Model in Image without auxiliary images The Model in Image domain home source type without auxiliary images (the WDT model and installation files are included in the same image with the WebLogic Server installation) is deprecated in WebLogic Kubernetes Operator version 4.0.7. Oracle recommends that you use Model in Image with auxiliary images .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Known limitations</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/known-limitations/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 08:14:59 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/known-limitations/index.html</guid>
      <description>The following sections describe known limitations for WebLogic Kubernetes Operator. Each issue may contain a workaround or an associated issue number.&#xA;NGINX SSL passthrough ingress service does not work with Kubernetes headless service ISSUE: When installing NGINX ingress controller with SSL passthrough enabled --set &#34;controller.extraArgs.enable-ssl-passthrough=true&#34;, any ingress rule created subsequently, using SSL passthrough to the individual server service, will fail.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>