<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Frequently asked questions on WebLogic Kubernetes Operator</title>
    <link>/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/faq/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Frequently asked questions on WebLogic Kubernetes Operator</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 08:14:59 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/faq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Coherence Requirements</title>
      <link>/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/faq/coherence-requirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 12:41:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/faq/coherence-requirements/</guid>
      <description>If you are running Coherence on Kubernetes, either inside a WebLogic domain or standalone, then there are some additional requirements to make sure that Coherence can form clusters.
Note that some Fusion Middleware products, like SOA Suite, use Coherence and so these requirements apply to them.
Unicast and Well Known Address When the first Coherence process starts, it will form a cluster. The next Coherence process to start (i.e. in a different pod) will use UDP to try to contact the senior member.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cannot Pull Image</title>
      <link>/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/faq/cannot-pull-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 08:08:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/faq/cannot-pull-image/</guid>
      <description>My domain will not start and I see errors like ImagePullBackoff or Cannot pull image
 When you see these kinds of errors, it means that Kubernetes cannot find your Docker image. The most common causes are:
 The image value in your domain resource is set incorrectly, meaning Kubernetes will be trying to pull the wrong image. The image requires authentication or permission in order to pull it and you have not configured Kubernetes with the necessary credentials, for example in an imagePullSecret.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>