<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Model in image :: WebLogic Kubernetes Operator</title>
    <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/samples/domains/model-in-image/index.html</link>
    <description>Sample for supplying a WebLogic Deploy Tooling (WDT) model that the operator expands into a full domain home during runtime.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 17:32:31 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/samples/domains/model-in-image/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prerequisites</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/samples/domains/model-in-image/prerequisites/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 17:32:31 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/samples/domains/model-in-image/prerequisites/index.html</guid>
      <description>Follow these prerequisite steps for WLS domain type.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auxiliary image creation</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/samples/domains/model-in-image/auxiliary-image-creation/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 17:32:31 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/samples/domains/model-in-image/auxiliary-image-creation/index.html</guid>
      <description>Create WebLogic images using the WebLogic Image Tool and WebLogic Deploy Tooling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Initial use case</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/samples/domains/model-in-image/initial/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 17:32:31 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/samples/domains/model-in-image/initial/index.html</guid>
      <description>Contents Overview Auxiliary image Deploy resources - Introduction Secrets Domain resource Verify the domain Verify the pods Invoke the web application Note Before you begin: Perform the steps in Prerequisites and then create a Model in Image auxiliary image by completing the steps in Auxiliary image creation .&#xA;Overview In this use case, you set up an initial WebLogic domain. This involves:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update 1</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/samples/domains/model-in-image/update1/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 17:32:31 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/samples/domains/model-in-image/update1/index.html</guid>
      <description>This use case demonstrates dynamically adding a data source to your running domain by updating your model and rolling your domain. It demonstrates several features of WDT and Model in Image:&#xA;The syntax used for updating a model is the same syntax you use for creating the original model. A domain’s model can be updated dynamically by supplying a model update in a file in a Kubernetes ConfigMap. Model updates can be as simple as changing the value of a single attribute, or more complex, such as adding a JMS Server. For a detailed description of model updates, see Runtime Updates .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update 2</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/samples/domains/model-in-image/update2/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 17:32:31 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/samples/domains/model-in-image/update2/index.html</guid>
      <description>This use case demonstrates concurrently deploying a domain that is similar to the Update 1 use case domain to the same sample-domain1-ns namespace, but with a different domain UID, a different WebLogic domain name, and a different WebLogic domain encryption key. It does this by:&#xA;Using the same image, image model YAML file, and application archive as the Initial and Update 1 use cases. Using the same model update ConfigMap source file as the Update 1 use case (a data source). Using a different (unique) domain UID, sample-domain2, for the new domain. Using a different (unique) domain name, domain2, for the different domains. Deploying secrets and a model update ConfigMap that are uniquely labeled and named for the new domain. Note that this use case shows Model in Image’s unique ability to quickly deploy a copy of a WebLogic domain that has a different WebLogic domain name and domain encryption key. This is a useful capability that is not supported by the Domain in Image domain home source type :</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update 3</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/samples/domains/model-in-image/update3/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 17:32:31 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/samples/domains/model-in-image/update3/index.html</guid>
      <description>The Update 3 use case demonstrates deploying an updated WebLogic application to the running Update 1 use case domain using an updated image.&#xA;In the use case, you will:&#xA;Create an image model-in-image:WLS-v2 that is similar to the currently active model-in-image:WLS-v1 image, but with the following updates: An updated web application v2 at the myapp-v2 directory path within the WDT application archive instead of myapp-v1. An updated model YAML file within the image that points to the new web application path. Apply an updated Domain YAML file that references the new image while still referencing the original Update 1 use case secrets and model ConfigMap. After the updated Domain YAML file is applied, the operator will:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update 4</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/samples/domains/model-in-image/update4/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 17:32:31 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/samples/domains/model-in-image/update4/index.html</guid>
      <description>This use case demonstrates dynamically changing the Work Manager threads constraint and data source configuration in your running domain without restarting (rolling) running WebLogic Servers. This use case requires that the Update 1 use case has been run and expects that its sample-domain1 domain is deployed and running.&#xA;In the use case, you will:&#xA;Update the ConfigMap containing the WDT model created in the Update 1 use case with changes to the Work Manager threads constraint configuration. Update the data source secret created in the Update 1 use case to provide the correct password and an increased maximum pool capacity. Update the Domain YAML file to enable the Model in Image online update feature. Update the Domain YAML file to trigger a domain introspection, which applies the new configuration values without restarting servers. Optionally, start a database (to demonstrate that the updated data source attributes have taken effect). Here are the steps:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cleanup</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/samples/domains/model-in-image/cleanup/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 17:32:31 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/samples/domains/model-in-image/cleanup/index.html</guid>
      <description>To remove the resources you have created in these samples:&#xA;Delete the resources associated with the domain.&#xA;$ /tmp/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/kubernetes/samples/scripts/delete-domain/delete-weblogic-domain-resources.sh -d sample-domain1 $ /tmp/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/kubernetes/samples/scripts/delete-domain/delete-weblogic-domain-resources.sh -d sample-domain2 This deletes the domain and any related resources that are labeled with the domain UID sample-domain1 and sample-domain2.&#xA;It leaves the namespace intact, the operator running, the load balancer running (if installed), and the database running (if installed).&#xA;NOTE: When you delete a domain, the operator will detect your domain deletion and shut down its pods. Wait for these pods to exit before deleting the operator that monitors the sample-domain1-ns namespace. You can monitor this process using the command kubectl get pods -n sample-domain1-ns --watch (ctrl-c to exit).</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>