<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>User Guide on WebLogic Kubernetes Operator</title>
    <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/userguide/</link>
    <description>Recent content in User Guide on WebLogic Kubernetes Operator</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:27:48 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/userguide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Operator prerequisites</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/userguide/prerequisites/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 16:40:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/userguide/prerequisites/introduction/</guid>
      <description>For the current production release 3.3.7 :
 Kubernetes 1.16.15+, 1.17.13+, 1.18.10+, 1.19.7+, and 1.20.6+ (check with kubectl version). Flannel networking v0.9.1-amd64 or later (check with docker images | grep flannel), Calico networking v3.16.1 or later, or OpenShift SDN on OpenShift 4.3 systems. Docker 18.9.1 or 19.03.1+ (check with docker version) or CRI-O 1.20.2+ (check with crictl version | grep RuntimeVersion). Helm 3.3.4+ (check with helm version --client --short). For domain home source type Model in Image, WebLogic Deploy Tooling 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supported platforms</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/userguide/platforms/environments/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 16:40:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/userguide/platforms/environments/</guid>
      <description>Contents  Supported environments Kubernetes, WebLogic Server, and operating system prerequisites Pricing and licensing  WebLogic Kubernetes Operator WebLogic Server Oracle Linux and WebLogic Server Images Reference   Important notes about specific environments  Oracle Cloud Infrastructure (OCI) Oracle Linux Cloud Native Environment (OLCNE) Oracle Private Cloud Appliance (PCA) and Oracle Private Cloud at Customer (OPCC) Microsoft Azure VMware Tanzu Kubernetes Grid (TKG) OpenShift WebLogic Server running in Kubernetes connecting to an Oracle Database also running in Kubernetes Development-focused Kubernetes distributions    Supported environments WebLogic Server and the operator are supported on Oracle Cloud offerings, such as:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Istio support</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/userguide/istio/istio/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 13:30:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/userguide/istio/istio/</guid>
      <description>Contents  Overview Limitations Determining the Istio version Setting up an operator with Istio support Creating a domain with Istio support  Setting up the domain namespace Configuring the domain resource Applying a Domain YAML file Exposing applications in Istio-enabled domains   Traffic management Distributed tracing Automatically added network channels  Added network channels for Istio versions prior to v1.10 Added network channel for Istio versions v1.10 and later Added network channel for WebLogic EJB and servlet session state replication traffic    Overview These instructions assume that you are using a Kubernetes cluster with Istio installed and configured already.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set up Kubernetes</title>
      <link>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/userguide/kubernetes/k8s-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 16:43:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oracle.github.io/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/userguide/kubernetes/k8s-setup/</guid>
      <description>Contents  Cheat sheet for setting up Kubernetes Set up Kubernetes on bare compute resources in a cloud  Prerequisites Quick start   Install Kubernetes on your own compute resources Install Docker for Mac with Kubernetes  Cheat sheet for setting up Kubernetes If you need some help setting up a Kubernetes environment to experiment with the operator, please read on! The supported environments are either an on-premises installation of Kubernetes, for example, on bare metal, or on a cloud provider like Oracle Cloud, Microsoft Azure, Google, or Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
