<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Frequently asked questions on WebLogic Kubernetes Operator</title>
    <link>/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/faq/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Frequently asked questions on WebLogic Kubernetes Operator</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 08:14:59 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/faq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Managing domain namespaces</title>
      <link>/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/faq/namespace-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 10:41:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/faq/namespace-management/</guid>
      <description>Each operator deployment manages a number of Kubernetes Namespaces. For more information, see Operator Helm configuration values. A number of Kubernetes resources must be present in a namespace before any WebLogic domain custom resources can be successfully deployed into it. Those Kubernetes resources are created either as part of the installation of the operator&amp;rsquo;s Helm chart, or created by the operator at runtime.
This FAQ describes some considerations to be aware of when you manage the namespaces while the operator is running.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cannot pull image</title>
      <link>/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/faq/cannot-pull-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 08:08:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/faq/cannot-pull-image/</guid>
      <description>My domain will not start and I see errors like ImagePullBackoff or Cannot pull image
 When you see these kinds of errors, it means that Kubernetes cannot find your Docker image. The most common causes are:
 The image value in your domain resource is set incorrectly, meaning Kubernetes will be trying to pull the wrong image. The image requires authentication or permission in order to pull it and you have not configured Kubernetes with the necessary credentials, for example in an imagePullSecret.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boot identity not valid</title>
      <link>/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/faq/boot-identity-not-valid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 08:08:19 -0401</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/faq/boot-identity-not-valid/</guid>
      <description>One or more WebLogic Server instances in my domain will not start and I see errors in the server log like this:
&amp;lt;Feb 6, 2020 12:05:35,550 AM GMT&amp;gt; &amp;lt;Authentication denied: Boot identity not valid. The user name or password or both from the boot identity file (boot.properties) is not valid. The boot identity may have been changed since the boot identity file was created. Please edit and update the boot identity file with the proper values of username and password.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Domain secret mismatch</title>
      <link>/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/faq/domain-secret-mismatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 08:08:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/faq/domain-secret-mismatch/</guid>
      <description>One or more WebLogic Server instances in my domain will not start and the domain resource status or the pod log reports errors like this:
Domain secret mismatch. The domain secret in DOMAIN_HOME/security/SerializedSystemIni.dat where DOMAIN_HOME=$DOMAIN_HOME does not match the domain secret found by the introspector job. WebLogic requires that all WebLogic Servers in the same domain share the same domain secret.
 When you see these kinds of errors, it means that the WebLogic domain directory&amp;rsquo;s security configuration files have changed in an incompatible way between when the operator scanned the domain directory, which occurs during the &amp;ldquo;introspection&amp;rdquo; phase, and when the server instance attempted to start.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disabling Fast Application Notifications</title>
      <link>/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/faq/fan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 17:20:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/faq/fan/</guid>
      <description>To support Fast Application Notifications (FAN), Oracle databases configure GRID (Oracle Grid Infrastructure). GRID is typically associated with (and required by) Oracle RAC databases but can also be used in other configurations. Oracle Autonomous Database-Serverless (ATP-S) does not provide GRID.
When connecting to a database that does not have GRID, the only type of WebLogic Server data source that is supported is the Generic Data Sources. Multi Data Sources and Active GridLink data sources cannot be used because they work with RAC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using OCI File Storage (FSS) for persistent volumes</title>
      <link>/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/faq/oci-fss-pv/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 12:12:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/faq/oci-fss-pv/</guid>
      <description>If you are running your Kubernetes cluster on Oracle Container Engine for Kubernetes (commonly known as OKE), and you use OCI File Storage (FSS) for persistent volumes to store the WebLogic domain home, then the file system handling demonstrated in the operator persistent volume sample will require an update to properly initialize the file ownership on the persistent volume when the domain is initially created.
File permission handling on persistent volumes can differ between cloud providers and even with the underlying storage handling on Linux based systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using an OCI load balancer</title>
      <link>/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/faq/oci-lb/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 12:41:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/faq/oci-lb/</guid>
      <description>If you are running your Kubernetes cluster on Oracle Container Engine for Kubernetes (commonly known as OKE), you can have OCI automatically provision load balancers for you by creating a Service of type LoadBalancer instead of (or in addition to) installing an ingress controller like Traefik or Voyager.
OKE Kubernetes worker nodes typically do not have public IP addresses. This means that the NodePort services created by the operator are not usable, because they would expose ports on the worker node&amp;rsquo;s private IP addresses only, which are not reachable from outside the cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Providing access to a PersistentVolumeClaim</title>
      <link>/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/faq/volumes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 15:02:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/faq/volumes/</guid>
      <description>I need to provide an instance with access to a PersistentVolumeClaim.
 Some applications need access to a file, either to read data or to provide additional logging beyond what is built into the operator. One common way of doing that within Kubernetes is to create a PersistentVolumeClaim (PVC) and map it to a file. The domain configuration can then be used to provide access to the claim across the domain, within a single cluster, or for a single server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Providing access to a ConfigMap</title>
      <link>/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/faq/configmaps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 15:02:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/faq/configmaps/</guid>
      <description>I need to provide an instance with access to a ConfigMap.
 Configuration files can be supplied to Kubernetes Pods and Jobs by a ConfigMap, which consists of a set of key-value pairs. Each entry may be accessed by one or more operator-managed nodes as a read-only text file. Access can be provided across the domain, within a single cluster, or for a single server. In each case, the access is configured within the serverPod element of the desired scope.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>External WebLogic clients</title>
      <link>/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/faq/external-clients/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 21:23:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/faq/external-clients/</guid>
      <description>Approaches There are two supported approaches for giving external WebLogic EJB or JMS clients access to a Kubernetes hosted WebLogic cluster: Load balancer tunneling and Kubernetes NodePorts.
This FAQ is for remote EJB and JMS clients - not JTA clients. The operator does not currently support external WebLogic JTA access to a WebLogic cluster, because external JTA access requires each server in the cluster to be individually addressable by the client, but this conflicts with the current operator requirement that a network channel in a cluster have the same port across all servers in the cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coherence Requirements</title>
      <link>/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/faq/coherence-requirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 12:41:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/faq/coherence-requirements/</guid>
      <description>If you are running Coherence on Kubernetes, either inside a WebLogic domain or standalone, then there are some additional requirements to make sure that Coherence can form clusters.
Note that some Fusion Middleware products, like SOA Suite, use Coherence and so these requirements apply to them.
Unicast and Well Known Address When the first Coherence process starts, it will form a cluster. The next Coherence process to start (for example, in a different pod), will use UDP to try to contact the senior member.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>